[{"id":469,"question":"The __________ Element represents a span of text that is isolated from it's surroundings for the purposes of bidirectional text formatting","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"B","answer_b":"Base","answer_c":"Bdo","answer_d":"Bdi","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":939,"question":"What is kubectl drain used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To safely evict all of your pods from a node before performing maintenance on the node","answer_b":"To stop all running containers in a pod","answer_c":"To get the status of a specific node during maintenance","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":945,"question":"Which of the following commands would show you the status of a Kubernetes deployment?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl rollout stats deployment\/Deployment","answer_b":"kubectl rollout status deployment\/Deployment","answer_c":"kubectl rollout log deployment\/Deployment","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":341,"question":"What is the best way to change table prefix (wp_) before installation in WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Before Installation: In this way, you have to rename your wp_config.php file according to your need through $table_prefix=\u2019wp_\u2019;.","answer_b":"Before Installation: Through this way, you have to go PHPMyAdmin -> Select your database -> Check all tables -> Add\/Update table prefix.","answer_c":"After Installation: Once you have the database, you can go ahead and change it","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":660,"question":"What is the option to mention field separator for the command \u2018cut\u2019","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-f","answer_b":"-c","answer_c":"-d","answer_d":"\\0","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":51,"question":"Which command can you use to re-execute a previous command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"!cat","answer_b":"!!","answer_c":"!a","answer_d":"!3","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"bash","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":592,"question":"What does the expression Exception::__toString means?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Exception::__String","answer_b":"Exception::__toString","answer_c":"Exception::_toString","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1039,"question":"With Ansible you can only use SSH key as it does not work with SSH password.","description":"You could either use SSH keys or you could use the -k argument and use SSH password instead.","answers":{"answer_a":"true","answer_b":"false","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":429,"question":"The problem that occurs when one transaction updates a database item and then the transaction fails for some reason is ________.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Dirty Read Problem","answer_b":"Temporary Modify Problem","answer_c":"Temporary Select Problem","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":339,"question":"Which of the following are not Numeric column types?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BIGINT","answer_b":"LARGEINT","answer_c":"SMALLINT","answer_d":"DOUBLE","answer_e":"DECIMAL","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":8,"question":"When do we use the GREP command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"When we want to search for a string","answer_b":"To find a file","answer_c":"To find a directory","answer_d":"To show all directories which have the string in their name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1017,"question":"What Is The Use Of Kube-controller-manager?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kube-controller-manager embeds the core control loop which is a non-terminating loop that regulates the state of the system.","answer_b":"kube-controller-manager embeds the core control loop which is a terminating loop that regulates the state of the system.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1019,"question":"Is Kubernetes open-source?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":702,"question":"Which command can be used to display basic information about your server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"uname","answer_b":"info","answer_c":"ls","answer_d":"show","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":48,"question":"Which of the answers listed below refers to a command used for invoking a text editor in Unix-like operating systems?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"edit","answer_b":"notepad","answer_c":"vi","answer_d":"bcdedit","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":155,"question":"Graphics defined by SVG is in which format?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CSS","answer_b":"XML","answer_c":"HTML","answer_d":"JSON","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":100,"question":"Which function is used to Strip whitespace (or other characters) from the beginning and end of a string?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"trim_str","answer_b":"strip_str","answer_c":"strip","answer_d":"trim","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":218,"question":"Which SQL statement is used to return only different values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DUPLICATE","answer_b":"DISTINCT","answer_c":"DIFFERENT","answer_d":"SELECT","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1082,"question":"If you wish to have something mounted when the server is booted in which file would you need to add it:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/etc\/fstab","answer_b":"\/etc\/boot","answer_c":"\/etc\/grub.conf","answer_d":"\/etc\/boot.conf","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1029,"question":"How to retrieve the join token for worker nodes in Docker Swarm?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker swarm join-token worker","answer_b":"docker get join-token worker","answer_c":"docker swarm get join-token worker","answer_d":"docker swarm join-token get worker","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"}]